(Leonard:)Do you understand that Stephanie's
not here to treat your imaginary ailments?
(Sheldon:)How is it imaginary that
I keep hearing an octave above middle C?
[HUMS]
(Sheldon:)Is that imaginary?
(Sheldon:)I don't think so.
[HUMS]
- Good night.
- Leonard, there's one more thing.
(Sheldon:)Article One, Section Three
of our roommate agreement.
(Sheldon:)- I'm calling an emergency meeting.
- No, you're not.
(Sheldon:)Leonard moves the meeting not occur.
Second? None heard, the motion fails.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to begin the meeting
by congratulating you on the progress...
(Sheldon:)...in your relationship with Dr. Stephanie.
(Leonard:)- Thank you.
- And that being said...
(Sheldon:)...we have to discuss the implementation
of the cohabitation rider...
(Sheldon:)...which has been activated
now that you're living together.
(Leonard:)- We're not living together.
- I beg to disagree. Ahem.
"A girlfriend shall be deemed, quote,
living with, unquote, Leonard...
...when she has stayed over,
A, 10 consecutive nights...
...or B, more than nine nights
in a three-week period, or C...